put lunch box
put bottle
grab sauce pan
put sauce pan
grab kettle
fill up kettle
put kettle
turn on kettle
grab sauce pan
turn on tap
fill sauce pan
pour water
grab quartz sponge
wash pan
Pour water
Turn off tap
Dry hands
Grab tea towel
Turn on hob
Put pan on hob
Stir pan
Grab cup
Open rice
Pour rice
Put cup
Close rice
Grab tea towel
Hang up tea towel
Open cupboard
Grab lunch box
Grab lids
Put lunch box
Close cupboard
open lunch box
put lid
grab bottle
pen bottle
fill bottle
shake bottle
pour bottle
fill bottle
turn off tap
\fill bottle
open fridge
grab squash
open squash
pour squash
put bottle
close squash
put squash in fridge
close bottle
shake
Check rim
Close bottle
Pour kettle
Put kettle
Put lid on rice
Grab salt
Open salt
Pour salt
Put salt inside
Put lid
Grab bottle
Close bottle
Open bottle
Check seal
Screw on lid
Put bottle in fridge
Open bottle
Fill bottle
Close lid
Shake bottle
Turn down hob
Open bottle
Pour out bottle
Fill bottle
Turn off tap
Close bottle
Put bottle in fridge
Close fridge
Turn on tap
Open cupboard
Put plate
Grab cutting board
Grab plates
Open cupboard
Put cutting board
Close cupboard
Put plates
Grab bowls
Open cupboard
Put bowls
Put measuring cup
Grab knife
Grab spatula
Open drawer
Put spatula
Put knife
Grab cutlery
Put knives
Put fork
Pour washing out liquid
Put washing out liquid
Move tap
Grab knives
place drawer
put knife
grab cutlery
put cutlery
grab plates
put plates
grab lid
put lid
grab tongs
grab glass
move lid
move tap
turn off tap
grab plate
wash plate
put plate on rack
drop plate
wash plate
put plate on rack
grad lid
wash lid
put lid on rack
grab plate
wash plate
put plate
grab glass
wash glass
put glass
grab tongs
wash tongs
put tongs
grab lid
wash lid
put lid
grab lunch box
wash lunch box
put lunch box
grab glass
wash glass
put glass
wash fork
put fork
wash knife
wash fork
put knife and fork
wash knife
put knife
put sponge
turn on tap
RINSE HANDS
TURN OFF TAP
DRY HANDS
MOVE SAUCEPAN
[END SUBTITLE]